Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Aziz Abu Hamad, Associate Director, 1984-1995
  - Subseries 1: Country Files, 1984-1995
    - Bahrain, 1982-1995
      - Al-Amal, 1990-1991 (Box 620, Folder 1)
      - Arrests, 1994-1995 (Box 620, Folder 2)
      - Background, 1989-1993 (Box 620, Folder 3)
      - Constitution--Legislative Decrees, 1982 (Box 620, Folder 4)
      - Demonstrations, 1994-1995 (Box 620, Folder 5)
      - Exile
        - Case Files, 1993 (Box 620, Folder 6)
        - Deportations, 1992 (Box 620, Folder 7)
        - Forced Exile, 1989-1994 (Box 620, Folder 8)
        - General, 1990-1994 (Box 620, Folder 9)
          [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2070]
        - Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 620, Folder 10)
      - General, 1987-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 620, Folder 11 to 12)
      - Human Rights, 1990-1994 (Box 620, Folder 13)
      - Other Side of Bahrain, 1992-1993 (Box 620, Folder 14)
      - Political Prisoners Case Files, 1987 (Box 620, Folder 15)
      - Torture, 1991-1992 (Box 620, Folder 16)
      - Trials, 1991-1992 (Box 620, Folder 17)
      - Voice of Bahrain, 1992-1995 (Box 620, Folder 18)
    - Kuwait, 1989-1995 (Box 621)
      - Middle East Watch (MEW)--Reports, 1990-1992, (3 Folders) (Box 621, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Abu-Hamad, Aziz, 1992
        - Incubators, 1992 (Box 621, Folder 4)
        - Report, 1990 (Box 621, Folder 5)
      - Asylum, 1991-1992 (Box 621, Folder 6)
      - Deportations, 1991-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 621, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Detainees List, 1991 (Box 621, Folder 9)
      - Detention
        - Conditions--Case Files, 1991, 1993-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 621, Folder 10 to 11)
          [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2071]
      - Disappearances, 1990 (Box 621, Folder 12)
      - Farhat, Naimat--Legal Case, 1991-1994
        - Case of Naimat Farhat in the Kuwaiti Courts, undated (Box 621, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1994, (6 Folders) (Box 621, Folder 14 to 19)
        - Meeting--Transcript, 1991 September 1 (Box 621, Folder 20)
      - Freedom of Association, 1993-1994 (Box 621, Folder 21)
      - Freedom of Press, 1991-1994 (Box 621, Folder 22)
      - Gulf War (Box 622)
        - Background, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 1)
        - General, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 2)
        - Human Rights Violations--Post-War--General, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 3)
        - POWs, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 4)
      - Human Rights Organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 5)
      - Incubators
        - Cemeteries, 1991 April 11 (Box 622, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence (Box 622, Folder 7)
        - Hospitals, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 8)
        - Interviews, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 9)
        - Press Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 622, Folder 10)
        - Reports
          - Kuwait’s ‘Stolen’ Incubators: The Widespread Repercussions of a Murky Incident, 1992 February 6 (Box 622, Folder 11)
          - Medical Ethics and Human Rights Violations: The Iraqi Occupation of Kuwait and Its Aftermath, undated (Box 622, Folder 12)
          - On Amnesty’s Report on Kuwait: the Killing of Premature Babies, 1991 January 14 (Box 622, Folder 13)
        - Testimony, 1990 October 10 (Box 622, Folder 14)
      - Interviews--Officials--Notes, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 15)
      - Iraqi Civilians, 1991 (Box 622, Folder 16)
      - Kuwaiti Association to Defend War Victims, 1991-1992 (Box 622, Folder 17)
      - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights--Internal Background Report, 1990 August 30 (Box 622, Folder 18)
      - Misinformation, 1990-1991 (Box 622, Folder 19)
      - Missing Persons
        - General, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 622, Folder 20)
        - Questionnaires, 1992, (4 Folders) (Box 622, Folder 21 to 24)
      - Mission, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 1)
      - Opposition Movement
        - Democracy Movement, 1989-1990 (Box 623, Folder 2)
        - Elections, 1992 (Box 623, Folder 3)
        - Exile Opposition, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 4)
        - General, 1990-1991 (Box 623, Folder 5)
        - Islamic Constitutional Movement, 1991 April 16 (Box 623, Folder 6)
        - Political Parties, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 7)
      - Palestinians
        - Asylum Case, 1991-1993 (Box 623, Folder 8)
        - Bedouin, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 9)
        - Gaza Palestinians, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 10)
        - Press Clippings, 1991-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 623, Folder 11 to 13)
        - Relations, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 14)
      - Physicians for Human Rights, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 15)
      - Post-War Reconstruction, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 16)
      - POWs, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 17)
      - Public Relations Efforts, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 18)
      - Refugees
        - General, 1993 (Box 623, Folder 19)
        - Interviews, 1990 (Box 623, Folder 20)
      - Resistance, 1990 (Box 623, Folder 21)
      - Torture--Cases
        - General, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 22)
        - Al-Adsani, Sulaiman, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 23)
        - Mubarak, Ahmad, 1994 (Box 623, Folder 24)
      - Trials
        - Al-Nida, 1991-1992 (Box 623, Folder 25)
        - Bush Assassination Attempt, 1993-1994 (Box 623, Folder 26)
        - Gulf War “Collaborators”, 1991-1993 (Box 623, Folder 27)
        - Martial Law, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 28)
        - State Security Courts, 1994-1995 (Box 623, Folder 29)
      - U.S. Congress, 1991 (Box 623, Folder 30)
    - Lebanon (Box 624)
      - al-Hayat--Chronologies--News Clips 1992, (5 Folders) (Box 624, Folder 1 to 5)
      - Amnesty International, 1991-1992 (Box 624, Folder 6)
      - Aoun, Gen. Michel
        - Amnesty and Exile, 1991-1993 (Box 624, Folder 7)
        - Surrender, 1990 October (Box 624, Folder 8)
      - Asylum Applications, 1992-1994 (Box 624, Folder 9)
      - Bernstein, Robert--Correspondence, 1994 (Box 624, Folder 10)
      - Centre for Lebanese Studies, 1994 (Box 624, Folder 11)
      - Council of Lebanese American Organizations (CLAO)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 624, Folder 12 to 14)
        - Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 624, Folder 15)
      - Economic Conditions, 1992 (Box 624, Folder 16)
      - Elections, 1991-1992 (Box 624, Folder 17)
      - Environment, 1993 (Box 624, Folder 18)
      - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1992-1993, (4 Folders) (Box 624, Folder 19 to 22)
      - Foreign Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 625, Folder 1)
      - General, 1993-1994, (5 Folders) (Box 625, Folder 2 to 6)
      - Haddad, Henriette, 1991-1992 (Box 625, Folder 7)
      - Hostages, 1991-1992, (5 Folders) (Box 625, Folder 8 to 12)
      - Human Rights Organizations, 1990-1994 (Box 625, Folder 13)
      - Internally Displaced, 1991-1993 (Box 625, Folder 14)
      - Israel--Press Clippings, 1984, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 626, Folder 1)
      - July, 1993
        - Articles, 1993 July-August (Box 626, Folder 2)
        - Background, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence--Israeli Embassy, July, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 4)
        - Damages--After, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 5)
        - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 6)
        - Interviews, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 7)
        - International Law, 1991 February 20 (Box 626, Folder 8)
        - Mission, 1993 October, (3 Folders) (Box 626, Folder 9 to 11)
        - NEXIS--Articles, 1993 July-August (Box 626, Folder 12)
        - Notes--South, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 13)
        - Operation Accountability Files, 1993 July
          - General, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 14)
          - Press Reports, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 15)
          - Wire Reports, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 16)
        - Press Notes--MEW, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 17)
        - Press Releases
          - General, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 18)
          - MEW, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 19)
        - Reaction
          - Arab World, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 20)
          - Egypt, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 21)
          - Hizbollah, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 22)
          - Iran, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 23)
          - United Nations, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 24)
          - United States, 1993 (Box 626, Folder 25)
        - Request for Information, 1993 August (Box 626, Folder 26)
        - Rone, Jemera--Methodology, 1991 (Box 626, Folder 27)
        - Testimony--Whitley, Andrew, 1992 September 15 (Box 626, Folder 28)
        - Wilcox Report, 1993 July (Box 626, Folder 29)
      - Khiam Prison, 1984-1994 (Box 626, Folder 30)
      - NGO Forum, 1991 (Box 626, Folder 31)
      - Palestinian Deportees, 1992-1993 (Box 626, Folder 32)
      - Trials, 1994 (Box 626, Folder 33)
      - United States--Press Clippings, 1988-1994 (Box 626, Folder 34)
- Series 3: Julie Friedman, 1978-1992
  - Subseries 1: Country Files, 1978-1992
    - Syria (Box 627)
      - Affidavit--Women in Prison, 1991 (Box 627, Folder 1)
      - Amnesties, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 2)
      - Arab World, 1989-1991 (Box 627, Folder 3)
      - Asylum, 1992 (Box 627, Folder 4)
      - Bibliographies, undated (Box 627, Folder 5)
      - Committee for the Defence of Palestinian Patriots Detained in Syria, 1989-1990 (Box 627, Folder 6)
      - Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners in Syria
        - Publications, undated (Box 627, Folder 7)
        - The Tribune, 1982-1986, 1990 (Box 627, Folder 8)
      - Domestic Affairs, 1989-1992 (Box 627, Folder 9)
      - Droits et Libertés en Syrie, 1983, 1985 (Box 627, Folder 10)
      - Drugs, 1991 (Box 627, Folder 11)
      - Elections, 1990 (Box 627, Folder 12)
      - Foreign Policy--Press Clippings, 1988-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 627, Folder 13 to 14)
      - Hama Massacre (1982 February 2)--Publications (Arabic), undated (Box 627, Folder 15)
      - Human Rights
        - Monitoring, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 16)
        - Violations, 1982-1991 (Box 627, Folder 17)
      - In the Bottom, 1985 (Box 627, Folder 18)
      - International Commission for the Defense of Human Rights in Syria--Annual Report, 1988 January (Box 627, Folder 19)
      - Iranian Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 20)
      - Iraq, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 21)
      - Israeli Relations--Peace Efforts, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 22)
      - Jews Syrian, 1989-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 627, Folder 23 to 24)
      - Media---NGO Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 25)
      - Middle East Peace Process, 1991 (Box 627, Folder 26)
      - National Alliance for Liberation of Syria--Free Syria, 1988-1989 (Box 627, Folder 27)
      - National Union of Syrian Students and Youth--Save Syrian Students, 1987 (Box 627, Folder 28)
      - NEXIS News Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 627, Folder 29)
      - Opposition, undated (Box 627, Folder 30)
      - Palestine Association for Human Rights, undated (Box 627, Folder 31)
      - Palestinian Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box 627, Folder 32)
      - Palestinian Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 627, Folder 33)
      - Party of Communist Action, 1988 (Box 627, Folder 34)
      - Political Participation, 1990-1992 (Box 627, Folder 35)
      - Post-Aoun Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 627, Folder 36)
      - Press Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 627, Folder 37)
      - Prisoners--Release, 1991 (Box 627, Folder 38)
      - Pro-Saddam Protests, 1990 (Box 627, Folder 39)
      - Publications--Human Rights--Arabic, 1991 (Box 627, Folder 40)
      - Publications--Human Rights--Arabic, 1991 (2 Folders)s (Box 628, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Syria Unmasked: The Suppression of Human Rights by the Asad Regime, 1991
        - Arabic Translation, 1991 (Box 628, Folder 3)
        - Reviews, 1991 (Box 628, Folder 4)
      - Travel Restrictions, 1991 (Box 628, Folder 5)
      - Trip Notes, 1990 July (Box 628, Folder 6)
      - United Nations, 1978, 1991-1992 (Box 628, Folder 7)
      - United States
        - Press Clippings, 19986 1989-1992, (5 Folders) (Box 628, Folder 8 to 12)
        - State Department
          - General, 1991 (Box 628, Folder 13)
          - Human Rights Report, 1990 (Box 628, Folder 14)
      - Update-MEW Report-Information and Changes, 1991 (Box 628, Folder 15)
- Series 4: Eric Goldstein, Research Director, 1986-1997
  - Subseries 1: Country Files, 1986-1997
    - Israel (Box 629)
      - Accountability Report (MEW), 1989-1990
        - Chevigny Drafts, 1989 (Box 629, Folder 1)
        - Feedback, 1989-1990 (Box 629, Folder 2)
        - Official Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 629, Folder 3)
        - Outline, undated (Box 629, Folder 4)
        - Rosenfeld, Fay, 1989 (Box 629, Folder 5)
        - Israel's Truth-Telling Without Accountability, 1991 September (Box 629, Folder 6)
      - B'Tselem: Israeli Information Center for Human Rights in the Occupied Territories, 1990-1991 (Box 629, Folder 7)
      - Collaborators, 1988-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 8 to 10)
      - Curfews, 1988-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 11 to 12)
      - Diaspora, 1988-1994 (Box 629, Folder 13)
      - Economic Developments, 1989-1991 (Box 629, Folder 14)
      - Education, 1988-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 15 to 17)
      - Extra-Judicial Sanctions, 1989-1990 (Box 629, Folder 18)
      - Family Reunification, 1989-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 19 to 20)
      - Foreign Relations
        - Egypt, 1987-1990 (Box 629, Folder 21)
        - Europe and Japan, 1990-1995 (Box 629, Folder 22)
        - Jordan, 1988-1994 (Box 629, Folder 23)
        - Morocco, 1991 (Box 629, Folder 24)
        - Third World, 1990-1992 (Box 629, Folder 25)
      - Gulf War Palestinians, 1990-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 26 to 28)
      - Intifada
        - Conditions--General, 1989-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 629, Folder 29 to 31)
        - Leaflets, 1989-1992 (Box 630, Folder 1)
        - The Price of Insurgency: Civil Rights in the Occupied Territories, 1988 (Box 630, Folder 2)
      - Journalists-Freedom of Expression, 1992-1994 (Box 630, Folder 3)
      - Judiciary, 1988-1994 (Box 630, Folder 4)
      - Land Issues, 1989-1994 (Box 630, Folder 5)
      - Laws of War, 1971-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 630, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Lawyers Human Rights, 1987-1994 (Box 630, Folder 8)
      - Medical Care, 1989-1995 (Box 630, Folder 9)
      - Military Courts, 1988-1993 (Box 630, Folder 10)
      - Mossad, 1990-1991 (Box 630, Folder 11)
      - Occupied Territories--General, 1987-1991 (Box 630, Folder 12)
      - Official Statements, 1987-1993 (Box 630, Folder 13)
      - Personalities
        - Al-Aqer, Dr. Mamdouh, 1991 (Box 630, Folder 14)
        - Ashrawi, Hanan, 1991 (Box 630, Folder 15)
        - Cohen, Stanley, 1992 (Box 630, Folder 16)
        - Demjanjuk, John, 1992-1993 (Box 630, Folder 17)
        - Feldman, Avigdor, 1986-1993 (Box 630, Folder 18)
        - Husseini, Faisal, 1989-1991 (Box 630, Folder 19)
        - General, 1989-1991 (Box 630, Folder 20)
        - Nathan, Abie, 1989-1991 (Box 630, Folder 21)
        - Nusseiba, Sari, 1991-1992 (Box 630, Folder 22)
        - Zucker, Dedi (David), 1988-1989 (Box 630, Folder 23)
      - Refugees, 1993-1995 (Box 630, Folder 24)
      - Restrictions on Demonstrations, 1989-1992 (Box 630, Folder 25)
      - Rule of Law, 1986-1994 (Box 630, Folder 26)
      - Settlements, 1988-1997, (5 Folders) (Box 631, Folder 1 to 5)
      - Shin Bet, 1987-1995 (Box 631, Folder 6)
      - Soviet Immigration, 1990-1993 (Box 631, Folder 7)
      - Taxes, 1989-1992 (Box 631, Folder 8)
      - Torture, 1986-1995, (5 Folders) (Box 631, Folder 9 to 13)
      - Travel Restrictions, 1989-1994 (Box 631, Folder 14)
      - United States
        - Bush Report, 1989-1991 (Box 631, Folder 15)
        - Embassy, 1985 December 31 (Box 631, Folder 16)
        - General, 1985-1994, (5 Folders) (Box 631, Folder 17 to 21)
        - General, 1990 July-1995 (31 files) (Box 632, Folder 1 to 31)
        - State Department Reports, 1988, 1990-1991, (3 Folders) (Box 632, Folder 32 to 34)
  - Subseries 2: Subject Files, 1987-1991
    - Middle East Watch--Eric Goldstein, 1987-1991
      - Correspondence, 1987-1991, (2 Folders) (Box 632, Folder 35 to 36)
      - Memos, 1987-1990 (Box 632, Folder 37)
- Series 5: Virginia Sherry, Associate Director, 1989-1993
  - Subseries 1: Country Files, 1989-1993
    - Iraq (Box 633)
      - Abdul Qassem al-Khoei, 1991 March (Box 633, Folder 1)
      - Aid/Arms Sales, 1990-1991 (Box 633, Folder 2)
      - Anfal/Other Past Abuses, 1992 (Box 633, Folder 3)
      - Arab American Medical Association, 1991 July (Box 633, Folder 4)
      - Arab Inter-State Relations--Post-War, 1991 (Box 633, Folder 5)
      - Assyrians, 1991 (Box 633, Folder 6)
      - Background/Overview, 1989-1991 (Box 633, Folder 7)
      - Developments, 1991 September-1991 December, (2 Folders) (Box 633, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Export Controls Against, 1991 (Box 633, Folder 10)
      - General--News Clippings, 1990 September-1992 August, (14 Folders) (Box 633, Folder 11 to 24)
      - General--News Clippings, 1992 September-December, (4 Folders) (Box 634, Folder 1 to 4)
        - Gulf War, 1990 August 1990-1991 February 28 (Box 634)
        - Causes of, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 5)
        - Course of (Box 634, Folder 6)
        - Financing, 1990-1991 (Box 634, Folder 7)
        - Follow-up, 1992-1993 (Box 634, Folder 8)
        - Highway Bombing, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 9)
        - Iraqi
          - Retreat, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 10)
          - Violations, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 11)
        - Media Issues, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 12)
        - Military
          - Civilian and Allied, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 13)
          - Iraqi, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 14)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 634, Folder 15)
        - Missile Attacks on Israel, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 16)
        - Operation Desert Shield--Post-War Information, 1991-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 634, Folder 17 to 18)
      - Harvard Study Team Report: Public Health in Iraq After the Gulf War, 1991 May (Box 634, Folder 19)
      - Human Rights Issues--Post-War, 1991 (Box 634, Folder 20)
      - Iran--Iraq Refugees, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 1)
      - Kuwait Border Demarcation, 1992 (Box 635, Folder 2)
      - Scandal, 1992 (Box 635, Folder 3)
      - War Crimes--Proposed U.S. Legislation, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 4)
      - Weapons--United Nations
        - Crisis, 1991 September (Box 635, Folder 5)
        - Iraqi, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 6)
      - Kurdistan Front--Iraq Negotiations, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 7)
      - Kurds--General, 1991-1992 (Box 635, Folder 8)
      - Kuwait
        - Post-War, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 9)
        - Prisoners, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 10)
      - Maps, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 11)
      - Mid-East Arms--Post-War, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 12)
      - Needless Deaths in the Gulf War (1991), 1989-1993
        - Casualties Analysis, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 13)
        - Press and Other Feedback, 1991-1992 (Box 635, Folder 14)
        - Back-up Materials, 1991 January-August, (8 Folders) (Box 635, Folder 15 to 22)
        - Civil Reports--Material Used and Cited in Draft, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 23)
        - Cultural Property Issues, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 24)
      - Notes--Sherry, Gini, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 25)
      - Nuclear Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 635, Folder 26)
      - Nutrition /Health Problems, 1991 (Box 635, Folder 27)
      - Operation Southern Watch, 1992 August (Box 636, Folder 1)
      - Opposition
        - General, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 2)
        - Post-War, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 3)
      - Personalities/Bios, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 4)
      - Political Analysis, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 5)
      - Political Opposition, 1991-1992 (Box 636, Folder 6)
      - Political Parties--Law of, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 7)
      - Post-Gulf War
        - Business, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 8)
        - Economic Moves--Reconstruction, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 9)
        - Political Developments, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 10)
      - Reparations, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 11)
      - Rules of War, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 12)
      - Sanctions
        - Embargo, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 13)
        - Issues, 1991 January-1991 December (Box 636, Folder 14)
        - Post-War, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 15)
      - Shia Issues, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 16)
      - Statistics, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 17)
      - Thallium Cases, 1992 March (Box 636, Folder 18)
      - Turkey’s Raids, 1991 October (Box 636, Folder 19)
      - United Nations
        - High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR), 1991 (Box 636, Folder 20)
        - Racial Discrimination, 1988-1989 (Box 636, Folder 21)
        - Resolutions
          - Gulf Crisis/War, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 22)
          - Post-War, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 23)
      - United States
        - Aid--General and Comparative, 1990-1991 (Box 636, Folder 24)
        - Policy
          - General, 1991 January-1991 April, (2 Folders) (Box 636, Folder 25 to 26)
          - Mid-East
            - General, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 27)
            - Pro-West Arab States’ Policy, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 28)
          - Post-War, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 29)
          - State Department Briefings--Transcripts, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 636, Folder 30 to 31)
      - Uprisings, 1991
        - General, 1991 March-April, (2 Folders) (Box 636, Folder 32 to 33)
        - Northern Iraq, 1991 April-June, (2 Folders) (Box 636, Folder 34 to 35)
        - Post-Uprising Military Clashes, 1991 (Box 636, Folder 36)
        - Related Issues, 1991 June (Box 636, Folder 37)
        - Southern Iraq, 1991 April (Box 636, Folder 38)
      - Williams, Jacqueline--Interviews--London, 1991 May (Box 636, Folder 39)
- Series 6: Publications, 1989-1991
  - Middle East International, 1989 December 1991, (3 Folders) (Box 637, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Mideast Mirror, 1990-1991 March, (5 Folders) (Box 637, Folder 4 to 8)
  - Mideast Mirror, 1991 April-August, (5 Folders) (Box 638, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Mideast Mirror, 1991 September-December, (4 Folders) (Box 639, Folder 1 to 4)